Tristan Hornsey-Pennell

UI Designer

એ 07976045773





thpUldesign@gmail.com



London, UK

Profile

When I was about 4 years old, my brother, my dad and I spent the afternoon on the family computer designing a spaceship control panel (an A4 sheet of paper with a few circles, squares and labels) that we attached to our beds to power the thrusters, shields and weapons so we could defeat and escape the night monsters. We collaborated, iterated and had fun doing it. Nearly 25 years later this is still one of my favourite memories of the three of us together - and a feeling I get to revisit everytime I design.

Experience

Product Designer SpoonSource, 2020-Present

A Stockholm based startup in it's infancy. My responsibilities here include collaborating with the Lead Product Designer on defining the brand guidelines, as well as:

- Supporting the building of a Design System (in Figma)
- Coordinating with external development team
- Gathering user feedback of website

People Operations Planner Apple, 2020-Present

Working as part of a small team to support over 100 employees around engagement, scheduling and development all while dealing with the unprecedented challenges COVID-19 presented:

- Coordinated 5 month development workshop series for retail teams that included managing a filming schedule, creating and designing Keynote content, selecting and training the presenters, and liaising with in store leadership teams around content
- Adjusted workshops for corporate talent team after interest was registered by them to use it to support the transition of team members from retail stores to corporate
- Rewrote the handbook on in store health and safety guidelines and reporting processes with the event of COVID-19

Merchandising and Internal Technologies Manager Apple, 2017-2020

Bridging the gap between corporate and retail teams, responsibilities in role included managing mulitple NPI's throughout the year, being responsible for implementing and training the store teams around any new in-store use technologies (i.e. new POS or diagnostic systems), other examples include:

- Team Leader on multiple high profile planogram changes
- Implemented new in store customer flows based on user feedback, that saw a high success rate in customer engagement which was then rolled out across the UK and Northern Europe
- Developed design guidelines for internal communication within the South UK market
- Increased stores profile within the EMEA market to the point where we became a go to store for testing any new in-store technologies or merchandising innovations

Skills

Responsive Web Design Rapid Prototyping Wireframing User Research Iconography Typography Design for Web **Android** iOS

Software

Figma Adobe XD Sketch invision + invision Studio UsabilityHub Photoshop Illustrator Blender iWork Microsoft Office

Education

Career Foundry **UI** Design

KEVICC

2020

A Level Law Psychology **Business** Philosophy 2005 - 2007

South Devon Waldorf School **GCSE**

1997 - 2005

Interests

I'm a huge music fan, somehow I managed to go to over 50 concerts last year, and I survived them all!

I worked as a chef for a few years so I love to cook.